Finding Aid for the North American New Music Festival Archive, 1983-1995
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Photographs 1983-1993, VI.; Items 1-173
  - Michael Udow in formal wear, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 4 inches; Kalmbach, Bob (Box 12, Item NAP-108)
  - Michael Udow in casual dress, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 5 x 3 inches; Kalmbach, Bob (Box 12, Item NAP-109)
  - Frances-Marie Uitti playing cello with Yvar Mikhashoff, pianist, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Riemens, Wim (Box 12, Item NAP-110)
  - Francis-Marie Uitti with cello, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 6 x 4 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-111)
  - Joaquin Valdepeñas playing clarinet, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 9 x 6 inches; Andrusz, Marlene (Box 12, Item NAP-112)
  - Gabriel Valverde, undated, 1 color photograph, 4 x 4 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-113)
  - James Van Demark with double bass, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 7 inches; Schaaf, Peter (Box 12, Item NAP-114)
  - Nils Vigeland, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 3.5 x 5 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-115)
  - Andre Watts, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-116)
  - James Willey, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7 x 5 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-117)
  - James Willey, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Ouzer, Louis (Box 12, Item NAP-118)
  - Jan Williams with mallets and marimba, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Harry, Don (Box 12, Item NAP-119)
  - Robin Kay Willoughby, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 8 inches; Willoughby, Robert (Box 12, Item NAP-120)
  - La Monte Young, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 10 x 7 inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-121)
  - La Monte Young, with mountains in the background, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7 x 9inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-122)
  - La Monte Young, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 7 x 9inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-123)
  - Frank Zappa, undated, 1 Black and white photograph, 9 x 6inches; Unidentified (Box 12, Item NAP-124)
  - B & W contact-sheet of 35mm images, including John Bergamo, Jan Williams, Leroy Jenkins, Colin Bright, undated, 1 black and white contact-sheet of 35mm images, 8 x 10 inches; Haupt, Irene (Box 12, Item NAP-125)
  - B&W contact sheet of 35mm images, including Chester Mais, Poul Ruders, Jan Williams, Colin Bright, Yvar Mikhashoff, undated, 1 black and white contact-sheet of 35mm images, 8 x 10 inches; Haupt, Irene (Box 12, Item NAP-126)
  - B&W contact-sheet of 35mm images of Diamanda Galas, undated, 1 black and white contact-sheet of 35mm images, 8 x 10 inches; Haupt, Irene (Box 12, Item NAP-127)
  - B&W contact-sheet of 35mm images, including Jan Williams, Frank Cipolla, Malcolm Goldstein, Joseph Celli, David Moss, 1985, 1 black and white contact-sheet of 35mm images, 8 x 10 inches; Haupt, Irene (Box 12, Item NAP-128)
  - B&W contact-sheet of 35mm images, including Philip Glass, Jon Gibson, Yvar Mikhashoff, Lejaren Hiller, Thomas Halpin, 1987, 1 black and white contact-sheet of 35mm images, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 12, Item NAP-129)
  - B&W contact-sheet of 35mm images, including Jan Williams, David Felder, János Négyésy, Thomas Halpin, Ralph Shapey, 1987, 1 black and white contact-sheet of 35mm images, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 12, Item NAP-130)
  - B&W contact-sheet of 35mm images, including John Cage, Morton Feldman, Jan Williams, 1987, 1 black and white contact-sheet of 35mm images, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 12, Item NAP-131)
  - B&W contact sheet of 35mm images, including Yvar Mikhashoff, Jan Williams, Lejaren Hiller, Ralph Shapey, Joseph Celli, Carol Plantamura, Jacob Druckman, 1987, 1 black and white contact-sheet of 35mm images, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 12, Item NAP-132)
  - B&W contact-sheet of 35mm images, including Jan Williams, Joel Chadabe, Yvar Mikhashoff, Otto Luening, Carol Plantamura, 1987, 1 black and white contact-sheet of 35mm images, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 12, Item NAP-133)
  - B&W contact-sheet of 35mm images, including Otto Luening, Lejaren Hiller, Yvar Mikhashoff, Thomas Halpin, 1987, 1 black and white contact-sheet of 35mm images, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 12, Item NAP-134)
  - Color contact sheet of 35mm images, including Lejaren Hiller, Philip Glass, Allen Sigel, Yvar Mikhashoff, Jan Williams, Stephen Manes, 1987, 1 color contact-sheet of 35mm images, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 12, Item NAP-135)
  - John Cage at the World Premiere of Music for seven musicians, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-136)
  - John Cage signing autographs, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-137)
  - John Cage after performance, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-138)
  - John Cage signing an autograph, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-139)
  - Robert Dick playing flute, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-140)
  - Jacob Druckman conducting the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-141)
  - Jacob Druckman conducting the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-142)
  - Jacob Druckman conducting the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-143)
  - David Felder and Janet Booth, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-144)
  - Morton Feldman, Barbara Monk Feldman, and Nina Freudenheim, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-145)
  - Philip Glass and unidentified female, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-146)
  - Philip Glass and Jon Gibson, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-147)
  - Lejaren Hiller and Lawrence Brose, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-148)
  - Lejaren Hiller and Bud Jacobs, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-149)
  - Lejaren Hiller, Ralph Shapey, and Jan Williams, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-150)
  - Otto Luening, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-151)
  - Otto Luening, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-152)
  - Otto Luening, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-153)
  - Otto Luening and Joel Chadabe, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-154)
  - Otto Luening, Joel Chadabe, and Carol Plantamura, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-155)
  - Otto Luening and Joel Chadabe, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-156)
  - Otto Luening and Jan Williams, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-157)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff performing with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-158)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff performing with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-159)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff performing with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-160)
  - Nils Vigeland on piano and Jan Williams on piano, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-161)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff on piano and Jan Williams on percussion, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-162)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff, Jan Williams, Bud Jacobs, and Paul Goodman, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-163)
  - Joel Chadabe and Yvar Mikhashoff, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-164)
  - Janos Negyesy and Joseph Celli, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-165)
  - Carol Plantamura, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-166)
  - Carol Plantamura and Jan Williams, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-167)
  - Ralph Shapey and Sheldon Berlow, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-168)
  - Allen Sigel, Ronald Richards, Phyllis Sigel, and Judy Koon, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-169)
  - Jan Williams, Joel Chadabe, and Yvar Mikashoff, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-170)
  - Jan Williams and unidentified male, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-171)
  - Jan Williams playing drums, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-172)
  - Jan Williams playing drums, 1987, 1 Black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mandolfo, Michael (Box 13, Item NAP-173)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Contributors
Mikhashoff, Yvar; Williams, Jan, 1939-; Metz, Donald
Subjects
Music--20th century; Music festivals--New York (State)--Buffalo; North American New Music Festival (Buffalo, N.Y.)
Genres
Clippings; Correspondence; Reviews; Photographs
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
North American New Music Festival Catalog, 1983-1993
List of musical programs in the concert series.